From the author of Rainbow Six.
Tom Clancy's Without Remorse is a action, thriller,
war film directed by Stefano Sollima.
An elite Navy SEAL uncovers an international conspiracy while
seeking justice for the murder of his pregnant wife.
John Kelly, played by Michael B. Jordan.
Robert Ritter, played by Jamie Bell.
Thomas Clay, played by Guy Pearce.
Karen Greer, played by Jodie Turner-Smith.
Pam Kelly, played by Lauren London.
Victor Rykov, played by Brett Gelman.
Without Remorse (also known as Tom Clancy's Without Remorse) is a 2021 American action thriller
film directed by Stefano Sollima and written by Taylor Sheridan and Will Staples.
It is based on the 1993 novel of the same name by Tom Clancy.
The film stars Michael B.
Jordan, Jamie Bell, Jodie Turner-Smith, Luke Mitchell, Jack Kesy, Brett
Gelman, Lauren London, Colman Domingo and Guy Pearce.
In the film, John Kelly, a U.S.
Navy SEAL, seeks revenge after his wife and unit
members are killed by Russian hitmen.
The film had been in development since the novel was published in 1993, with various actors,
including Keanu Reeves and Tom Hardy, approached for the role of John Kelly.
After over 20 years in development hell, Jordan was announced as the lead role in September
2018, and Sheridan was hired to rewrite a script originally written in the 1990s.
Filming began in Berlin in October 2019 and
completed production in October 2020.
Without Remorse was originally produced and set for a theatrical release by Paramount Pictures, but was delayed
and then acquired by Amazon Studios, who digitally released it on Prime Video on April 30, 2021.
The film received mixed reviews from critics with praise for Jordan's performance,
action sequences and technical aspects, but called the film generic.
The tone is intense.